Guide to the George B. Post Architectural Records circa 1860–1997 (bulk, 1880–1980) PR 53
New-York Historical Society
- Series V. Photographs and other material, 41.1 Linear feet in 32 boxes.
  - Subseries V.B. Photographs, clippings, etc, 23.23 Linear feet in 19 boxes.
    - Photos: M-1 (Offsite-box 65)
      Drawings for a memorial Gateway for Union College (4 prints of drawings)
      Views of decoration of crown of Great Dome by Blashfield, Wisc. State Capitol
      Cleveland Trust Co. plaster model
      "Court of All Nations"
      "Excelsior" plaster model
      Defense of the Union monument, 1861-1865
      Iron Gate-Mills Building
      Wisconsin State Capitol / newspaper article
      America's Greatest monument, "Court of All Nations"
    - Photos: M-2 (misc. commercial buildings) (Offsite-box 66)
      College of the City of New York
      Detail of lower stories, Hotel Statler, St. Louis, MO
      New York Stock Exchange
      Sinton Building?
      Unidentified
      The Prudential Insurance Co. of America
    - Clippings scrapbook: Vanderbilt Cotton Exchange; Produce Exchange (Offsite-box 110, Folder 1)
    - Clippings scrapbook: Mills Building; Morristown Library; New York State Capitol; Western Union Building (Broadway & Dey Streets) (Offsite-box 110, Folder 2)
    - Clippings scrapbook: New York Times Building; Equitable Building (Offsite-box 110, Folder 3)
    - Clippings scrapbook: Pulitzer Building ("World Building"); Hamilton Club; 22nd Street Armory (Offsite-box 110, Folder 4)
    - Clippings scrapbook: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 110, Folder 5)
    - City College of New York (C.C.N.Y.) (Offsite-box 110, Folder 6)
    - City College of New York: interior & exterior "36" (Offsite-box 110, Folder 7)
    - City College of New York (C.C.N.Y.) (Offsite-box 110, Folder 8)
    - The Board of Higher Education of the City of New York. Proposal for Bids, Contracts, Bond and Specifications, 1930 (Offsite-box 110, Folder 9)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1882-1891 (Offsite-box 110, Folder 10)
    - Unidentified (Offsite-box 110, Folder 11)
    - [Unidentified?] (Offsite-box 111, Folder 1)
    - [Unidentified?] (Offsite-box 111, Folder 2)
    - Clippings scrapbook (Offsite-box 111, Folder 3)
    - Clippings scrapbook (Offsite-box 111, Folder 4)
    - Clippings scrapbook (Offsite-box 111, Folder 5)
    - Clippings scrapbook (Offsite-box 111, Folder 6)
    - Competitions, sketches, ideas (Offsite-box 111, Folder 7)
    - Specifications for apartment house (Ansonia Co.) [Ansonia, Colorado? Connecticut?], 1919 July 22 (Offsite-box 111, Folder 8)
    - Model - Sculpture. Wisconsin State Capitol (Offsite-box 111, Folder 9)
    - Morris County Golf Club (Convent, New Jersey) (Offsite-box 112, Folder 1)
    - Clubs (miscellaneous, in alphabetical order) (Offsite-box 112, Folder 2)
    - Cleveland Trust Co., Wade Park Branch (Cleveland, Ohio) (Offsite-box 112, Folder 3)
    - National Town and Country Club: Cleveland, Ohio, and New York Chapter (Offsite-box 112, Folder 4)
    - Glens Falls Insurance Co. (Glens Falls, New York) (Offsite-box 112, Folder 5)
    - Prudential Insurance Co. (Newark, NJ) (Offsite-box 112, Folder 6)
    - New York Stock Exchange (Offsite-box 112, Folder 7)
    - Samaritan Hospital (Troy, New York) (Offsite-box 112, Folder 8)
    - Hospitals (Offsite-box 112, Folder 9)
    - Hospitals. New Jersey Sanatorium (Offsite-box 112, Folder 10)
    - Stamford Hospital (Stamford, Connecticut) (Offsite-box 112, Folder 11)
    - Hotels (miscellaneous, in alphabetical order) (Offsite-box 112, Folder 12)
    - Commercial buildings (miscellaneous, in alphabetical order) [1 of 2] (Offsite-box 113, Folder 1)
    - Commercial buildings (miscellaneous, in alphabetical order) [2 of 2] (Offsite-box 113, Folder 2)
    - Government Buildings Misc. Alphabetical (2) Wisconsin State Capitol (int + ext photos) (Offsite-box 113, Folder 3)
    - Government Buildings Misc. Alphabetical (1) (Offsite-box 113, Folder 4)
    - Commercial buildings; St. Paul Building (Broadway & Ann Street) (Offsite-box 113, Folder 5)
    - Hotel Cleveland (Cleveland, Ohio) (Offsite-box 114, Folder 1)
    - Gould Hotel (Seneca Falls, New York) (Offsite-box 114, Folder 2)
    - Statler Hotel (Boston, Massachusetts), 1925 (Offsite-box 114, Folder 3)
    - Statler Hotel (Buffalo, New York) (Offsite-box 114, Folder 4)
    - Statler Hotel (Cleveland, Ohio) (Offsite-box 114, Folder 5)
    - Statler Hotel (Cleveland, Ohio) (Offsite-box 114, Folder 6)
    - Statler Hotel (St. Louis, Missouri) (Offsite-box 114, Folder 7)
    - Syracuse Hotel (Syracuse, New York) (Offsite-box 114, Folder 8)
    - Wade Park Manor Hotel (Cleveland, Ohio), 1920-1923 (Offsite-box 114, Folder 9)
    - Religious structures (miscellaneous, in alphabetical order) (Offsite-box 114, Folder 10)
    - George Washington University (Offsite-box 115, Folder 1)
    - Union College (Schenectady, New York) (Offsite-box 115, Folder 2)
    - Carnegie Technical Schools (Pittsburgh Pennsylvania) (Offsite-box 115, Folder 3)
    - Baskingridge Sunday School (Offsite-box 115, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous incl. N.Y. World's Fair 1939 Theaters (Offsite-box 115, Folder 5)
    - Photos Ritz Tower Photos of Perspective by Wurts Bros. (E. Roth) 57th St. and Park Ave. (Offsite-box 115, Folder 6)
    - Specimens of George B. Post envelopes which contained photos now housed in acid-free folders (Offsite-box 115, Folder 7)
    - Unidentified (Offsite-box 115, Folder 8)
    - Unidentified (Offsite-box 115, Folder 9)
    - Unidentified [The Architectural Record] (Offsite-box 116, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified [Hotel Management] (Offsite-box 116, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous unidentified (Offsite-box 116, Folder 3)
    - Governor Clinton Hotel (Offsite-box 116, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous unidentified (Offsite-box 116, Folder 5)
    - Unidentified (Offsite-box 116, Folder 6)
    - Clipping drawers (Offsite-box 116, Folder 7)
    - Old personnel records (More recent records in card file in Geo. B. Post & Sons safe) (Offsite-box 116, Folder 8)
    - Unidentified [2 folders] (Offsite-box 117, Folder 1-2)
    - Miscellaneous unidentified (Offsite-box 117, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified [The Roosevelt] (Offsite-box 117, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified [The Architectural Forum] (Offsite-box 117, Folder 5)
    - Unidentified [The Statler Idea] (Offsite-box 117, Folder 6)
    - Warwick Hotel (New York City) (Offsite-box 118, Folder 1)
    - Union Trust Company (New York) (Offsite-box 118, Folder 2)
    - Commercial buildings (miscellaneous, in alphabetical order); plans of Smith Building (Offsite-box 118, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified (Offsite-box 118, Folder 4)
    - [Unidentified?] (Offsite-box 119, Folder 1)
    - George B. Post houses (Miscellaneous, in alphabetical order) (Offsite-box 119, Folder 2)
    - Houses. Walter E. Kelly residence (Riverdale, New York) (Offsite-box 119, Folder 3)
    - Eclipse Park Development (Beloit, Wisconsin) (Offsite-box 119, Folder 4)
    - Collis P. Huntington House (Offsite-box 119, Folder 5)
    - F. G. Lloyd residence (Bernardsville, New Jersey) (Offsite-box 119, Folder 6)
    - "Claremont," George B. Post residence (Bernardsville, New Jersey) (Offsite-box 119, Folder 7)
    - Cornelius Vanderbilt or Collis P. Huntington (Offsite-box 119, Folder 8)
    - Vocational Building, City College of New York (C.C.N.Y.). Photograph of perspective by Wurts Bros. #121284, 1929 April 30 (Offsite-box 119, Folder 9)
    - Structural steel construction log for Main Building, City College of New York (C.C.N.Y.). (Offsite-box 119, Folder 10)
    - [Structural steel construction log for Main Building, City College of New York (C.C.N.Y.).?] (Offsite-box 120, Folder 1)
    - Clubs. National Town and Country Club: Cleveland, Ohio, and New York Chapter (Offsite-box 120, Folder 2)
    - Statler Hotel (Buffalo, New York) (Offsite-box 120, Folder 3)
    - Roosevelt Hotel (New York City) (Offsite-box 120, Folder 4)
    - [Roosevelt Hotel (New York City)?] (Offsite-box 120, Folder 5)
    - New York Stock Exchange (Offsite-box 121, Folder 1)
    - Hotels. Miscellaneous (in alphabetical order) (Offsite-box 121, Folder 2)
    - Prudential Insurance Co. (Newark, New Jersey) (Offsite-box 121, Folder 3)
    - Government Buildings Misc. Alphabetical Wisconsin State Capitol, Plan of Ground Floor (Offsite-box 121, Folder 4)
    - Masonic Temple (Greenwich, Connecticut) (Offsite-box 121, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, including 1939 New York World's Fair theatres (Offsite-box 121, Folder 6)
    - F.C. Newcomber Apartments (Euclid Heights, Cleveland), 1922 (Offsite-box 121, Folder 7)
    - Crisp Apartments (602-608 East 84th Street, New York, N.Y.), 1928 (Offsite-box 121, Folder 8)
- Series VI. 2002 Accrual, 1894-1997; 354 Linear feet in 147 boxes.
  - Subseries VI.A. Administrative Files, 1894-1997, undated; 6 Linear feet in 6 boxes.
    - Client File, A-Z (card file), undated (Offsite-box 1, Enclosure 1-A)
      This index provides alphabetical access to the project files in Subseries VI.C. A photocopy is also available from the librarian in the New-York Historical Society's Department of Prints, Photographs, and Architectural Collections.
    - Client File, A-Z (card file; projects 1870-1933), undated (Offsite-box 1, Enclosure 1-B)
    - Historical and biographical files, 1940-1963, undated (Offsite-box 2-A)
    - Historical and biographical files, 1940-1997, undated (Offsite-box 2-B)
    - Ledgers (bills and receipts; disbound), 1918-1958 (Offsite-box 3-A)
    - Ledgers (bound). Volume 1, 1894-1899 (Offsite-box 3-B)
    - Ledgers (bound). Volume 2, 1899-1910 (Offsite-box 3-B)
    - Ledgers (bound). Volume 3, 1910-1918 (Offsite-box 3-B)
    - Company Rolodex, undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Miscellaneous contracts, [undated?] (Offsite-box 4)
  - Subseries VI.B. Prospective Correspondence, 1937-1964; 2 Linear feet in 2 boxes.
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1937-1964, undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1937-1964, undated (Offsite-box 6)
  - Subseries VI.C. Project Files, 1911-1989; 51.83 Linear feet in 53 boxes.
    George B. Post & Sons assigned numerical identifiers to each project file, the first two digits representing the year, and the subsequent digits (separated by a hyphen) representing the job number. Some numbers are preceded by an asterisk (*) or the letter "H," but the significance of these notations has been lost. For an index to the project files by client, see the A-Z card file in Subseries VI.A (Offsite Box 1, Enclosure 1-A). A photocopy of this index is also available from the librarian in the New-York Historical Society's Department of Prints, Photographs, and Architectural Collections. See also the corresponding rolled drawings in Subseries VI.F, which relate to these files.
    - Projects, 1926-1948 (Offsite-box 7-A)
      Hotels.
    - Projects, 1927-1942 (Offsite-box 7-B)
      Garages, hospitals, hotels.
    - Projects (40-494 through 47-1027), 1940-1952 (Offsite-box 8)
    - Projects (project numbers lacking), 1919-1941 (Offsite-box 9)
    - Projects (40-950 through 43-980), 1940-1941 (Offsite-box 10)
    - Projects (46-1000 through 49-1053), 1945-1951 (Offsite-box 11)
    - Projects (project numbers lacking), 1928-1954 (Offsite-box 12)
    - Projects (50-1055 through 53-1099), 1950-1952 (Offsite-box 13)
    - Projects (54-1117 through 54-1135), 1954 (Offsite-box 14)
    - Projects (52-1804 through 53-1109), 1953 (Offsite-box 15)
    - Projects (55-1137 through 56-1161), 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 16)
    - Projects (56-1155 through 56-1181), 1956 (Offsite-box 17)
    - Projects (57-1187 through 57-1204), 1957 (Offsite-box 18)
    - Projects (58-1208 through 58-1231), 1958 (Offsite-box 19)
    - Projects (59-1235 through 59-1258), 1959 (Offsite-box 20)
    - Projects (59-1258 through 63-1358), 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 21)
    - Projects (60-1273 through 60-1301A), 1960 (Offsite-box 22)
    - Projects (61-13[01?] through 61-1322), 1961 (Offsite-box 23)
    - Projects (61-3101 through 62-1345A), 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 24)
    - Projects (63-1346 through 63-1380), 1963 (Offsite-box 25)
    - Projects (64-1388 through 64-1414), 1964 (Offsite-box 26)
    - Projects (64-1390 through 65-1458), 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 27)
    - Projects (65-1422 through 65-1445), 1965 (Offsite-box 28)
    - Projects (65-1419 through 66-1475), 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 29)
    - Projects (66-1460 through 66-1470), 1966 (Offsite-box 30)
    - Projects (66-1463 through 66-1487), 1966 (Offsite-box 31)
    - Projects (67-1492 through 67-1523), 1967 (Offsite-box 32)
    - Projects (68-1539 through 68-1555), 1968 (Offsite-box 33)
    - Projects (69-1592 through 71-1672), 1969 (Offsite-box 34)
    - Projects (68-1549 + many unsorted), 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 35)
    - Projects (66-1470 through 71-1667), 1966-1971 (Offsite-box 36)
    - Projects (H70-1625 through 71-1655), 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 37)
    - Projects (H70-1625 through 71-1655), 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 38)
    - Projects (71-1655 through 71-1683), 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 39)
    - Projects (71-1683 through 72-1730), 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 40)
    - Projects (74-1778 through 74-1796), 1974 (Offsite-box 41)
    - Projects (72-1726 through 73-1746), 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 42-A)
    - Projects (75-1814 through 75-1833), 1975 (Offsite-box 42-B)
    - Projects (75-1804 through 76-1870), 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 43)
    - Projects (76-1835 through 76-1869), 1976 (Offsite-box 44)
    - Projects (77-1874 through 78-1908), 1977 (Offsite-box 45)
    - Projects (77-1879 through 78-1909), 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 46)
    - Projects (78-1925 through 79-1961), 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 47)
    - Projects (80-1988B through 81-2006), 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 48)
    - Projects (80-1988B through 80-2004), 1980 (Offsite-box 49)
    - Projects (81-2005 through 82-2056), 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 50)
    - Projects (83-2068 through 83-2094), 1983 (Offsite-box 51)
    - Projects (84-2096 through 86-2164), 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 52)
    - Projects (87-2168 through 88-2190), 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 53)
    - Projects (88-2209 through 89-2221B), 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 54)
    - Projects (various years), 1959-1987 (Offsite-box 55)
      A note inside this box indicates the contents were dropped during a transfer before they came to the New-York Historical Society, hence their lack of order.
    - Blueprints (folded): Various parks, circa 1936 (Offsite-box 56-A, Folder 1-2)
    - Binder (disbound): Hotel projects, circa 1911-1938 (Offsite-box 56-A, Folder 3-4)
    - Binder (disbound): Hotel Roanoke, Valeria Home, Eclipse Park, circa 1917-1950 (Offsite-box 56-B, Folder 1-5)
  - Subseries VI.D. Financial Records, 1969-1984; 1 Linear feet in 1 box.
    - Financial records, 1969-1984 (Offsite-box 57)
  - Subseries VI.E. Photographs and Periodicals, 1971-1976, undated; 2 Linear feet in 2 boxes.
    - Photographs, 1971-1976 (Offsite-box 58)
    - Periodicals, [undated?] (Offsite-box 59)
  - Subseries VI.F. Rolled Drawings, 1936-1993; 291 Linear feet in 83 boxes.
    Restriction
    The drawings in Subseries VI.F require one month to flatten and conserve before use.
    George B. Post & Sons assigned numerical identifiers to each project drawing, the first two digits representing the year, and the subsequent digits (separated by a hyphen) representing the job number. Some numbers are preceded by an asterisk (*) or the letter "H," but the significance of these notations has been lost. These rolls are presented in numerical order (which, except in the case of rolls containing multiple drawings, is also chronological order). For an index to these projects by client, see the A-Z card file in Subseries VI.A (Offsite Box 1, Enclosure 1-A). A photocopy of this index is also available from the librarian in the New-York Historical Society's Department of Prints, Photographs, and Architectural Collections. See also the corresponding project files in Subseries VI.C, which relate to these drawings.
    - 36-934 | Kathrine Le Roy (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-535)
    - 37-941 | All Drawings and Sketches District School Central School | Callicoon N. Y. Area (school district #1 town of [Dearware] | [illegible]) | Re: Post War School Planning | June 3rd 1943 (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-535)
    - 37-[unknown job number] | Woods Estate Subdivision Map (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-572)
    - 40-950 | Laundry Building Society of St. Johnland Kings Park | also kitchen alts 51-1077 (from Box 1) 51-1077 (Offsite-box RD-535)
    - 40-954 | Lumber Storage [Site] Cartaret, N.J. For I. T. [Williams] and Sons (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-535)
    - 41-963 | Peters, Isabel (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-572)
    - 41-966 | D. Scott Jr. Beach Home (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-533)
    - 43-979 | Fresh Air Camp (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-534)
    - 44-985 | Thomas Jefferson Hotel Charlottesville Prints Complete (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-533)
    - 44-985 | TJ. Inn Revised Schemes 1949 (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-534)
    - 44-985 | T. J. Inn Renderings Inn and Cottages preum elevations and plan (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-534)
    - 44-985 | T. J. Inn Negative Photostats of Working Drawing (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-534)
    - 44-[unknown job number] | 1944 Tract Speculation Cottage (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-535)
    - 45-993 | I. T. Williams Office Bldg. (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-535)
    - 45-994 | C. R. MacGregor (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-535)
    - 46-996 | Sketch of Proposed Additions to Jenks House, Kingston N.J. | part of [report] Re existing conditions for Mr. and Mrs. Stanley [Osborne] (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-533)
    - 46-1000 | Woodward (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-535)
    - 46-1001 | Potter Subdivision (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-535)
    - 46-1002 | Rye Methodist Church, NY (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-534)
    - 46-1004 | R. O. Post (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-534)
    - 46-1005 | Factory Building for Concrete Products Co. Brighton Mass (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-534)
    - 46-1006 | T. Peters Garden [us] Cottage (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-533)
    - 46-1010 | L. W. Williams (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-534)
    - 46-1011 | Brightwater Inn Alt. (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-534)
    - 46-1014 | WM Parsons Jr. (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-533)
    - [47]-1017 | Brooklyn Central Methodist Church (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-535)
    - 47-1019 | Tchudy (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-533)
    - 47-1020 | Williams (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-533)
    - 47-1021 | Original Bldg. N. Shore: Med. Group at Oakwood Ave. Huntington (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-535)
    - 47-1024 | Starke (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-533)
    - 47-1025 | W. M. B. Nichols Cottage [Syosset] (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-535)
    - 47-1026 | Callaway (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-535)
    - 47-1028 | Heroy Residence (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-535)
    - 47-1030 | Kipp. and Addition (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-535)
    - 1947-[unknown job number] | James Estate (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-572)
    - 48-1033 | St. Mary's hospital for children (from Box 6 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-507)
    - [48-1033] | St. Mary's Children's Hospital sketch groups (from Box 6 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-508)
    - 48-1033 | St. Mary's Hospital Supplementary dwgs. Not printed for Kaplan 1|83 (from Box 6 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-524)
    - 48-1033 | St. Mary's Hosp. Re Fire Doors (from Box 6) (Offsite-box RD-537)
    - 48-1034 | T. M. Peters (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-534)
    - 48-1035 | Post House, C. S. H. (from Box 3 of 4) (Offsite-box RD-571)
    - 48-1036 | Post Family Ledger Stones (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-535)
    - 48-1038 | Martin (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-534)
    - 48-1041 | F. M. Station (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-535)
    - 48-[unknown job number] | R. C. C. 1948 [O. H. Orr Res.] (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-534)
    - 49-1044 | W. V. Moffit (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-535)
    - 49-1049 | Winthrop Stimpson Office Alt. (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-533)
    - 49-1051 | Timmie Res. (from Box 1) (Offsite-box RD-535)
    - 50-1055 | Lincoln (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)
    - 50-1056 | C. S. H. East Side School District #8 | Original Job and Additions | Record Set Incl. Mechanical | (mech. tracings lost) | keep this Sept 1 55 (from Box 4) 54-1136 60-1290 (Offsite-box RD-553)
    - 50-1056 | East Side Elementary (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-573)
    - 50-1057 | A. Palmer (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-574)
    - 50-1058 | Hunt Res. (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-555)
    - 50-1059 | Arthur Andersen (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-573)
    - 50-1060 | Fisher (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)
    - 50-1061 | J. Smith (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-573)
    - 50-1063 | [Hewitt, Oglou, Benson, [illegible]] (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-574)
    - 50-[unknown job number] | R. V. Ingersoll (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-574)
    - 51-1065 | Stone, C. H. (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-545)
    - 51-1069 | Myers Residence (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)
    - 51-1070 | T. R. Williams | includes bay windows and elevator (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-574)
    - 51-1071 | General Telephone (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-574)
    - 51-1074 | Burk Lloyd Lane (from Box 3) (Offsite-box RD-556)
    - 51-1074 | Burr (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-574)
    - 51-1079 | Porter (bought by [Trottman]) (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-573)
    - 52-1074 | Stevens (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)
    - 52-[1080] | [N. S.] Medical (from Box 4) 60-[1295] (Offsite-box RD-552)
    - [52-1081] | Root Residence (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)
    - 52-1085 | Agnew (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)
    - 52-1086 | Rowland (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)
    - 52-1087 | Nielson (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-573)
    - 52-1087 | Pulsifer (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-573)
    - 52-1087 | Pulsifer L. I. House Prints | Not G. B. Post and Sons (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-573)
    - 52-1090 | Betts (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)
    - 52-1091 | Von Raits (from Box 3) 56-1179 (Offsite-box RD-566)
    - 52-1095 | [Rort] Cummings Res. (from Box 4) *61-1328 64-1410 (Offsite-box RD-553)
    - 53-1093 | Panfield Corp. L. H. (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-574)
    - 53-[1094] | [unknown job title] (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-574)
    - 53-1097 | C. S. H. West Side School Dist. 11 All Jobs (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-573)
    - 53-1098 | Huntington Federal Savings and Loan Tracings | found under [illegible] [West Jr. High] [illegible] June 16, 1971 (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-574)
    - 53-1098 | Huntington Federal Savings (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)
    - 53-[1102] | Ridder (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)
    - 53-1105 | Eisenman (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)
    - 53-1107 | Maw Tracings (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)
    - 53-1109 | Robert W. Chaplin - Wilton Conn. Alts. and Additions (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)
    - 53-1111 | E. T. Turner (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)
    - 53-1112 | Bonime (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)
    - 53-[unknown job number] | Steers [Development] R. C. C. (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)
    - 53/62/64/68/76-[unknown job number] | C. S. H Beach Club (from unnumbered box) (Offsite-box RD-563)
    - 54-1114 | Barclay (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-574)
    - 54-1117 | Rudley (from Box 5 of 6) (Offsite-box RD-532)
    - 54-1119 | Nunez (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-573)
    - 54-1121 | Osborne (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)
    - 54-1123 | Starke (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-574)
    - 54-1123-A | Alts. and Adds. Old Starke Res. Cove Road Oyster Bay Now McLanahan Jan 1956 (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)
    - 54-[1123] | E. K. (Ted) Chadin (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-574)
    - 54-1126 | Smoot (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-574)
    - 54-1128 | D. Brown Res. and Garage (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)
    - 54-1130 | 14 E - 48th St. | 60 E - 55th St. | Re: Vission (from Box 2) (Offsite-box RD-578)